[
    {
        "question": "[     ] 있어요?",
        "trans": "Do you have a girlfriend?",
        "option1": "친구",
        "option2": "남자친구",
        "option3": "여자친구",
        "option4": "친구들",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 1",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
   
    {
        "question": "[     ] 있어요?",
        "trans": "Do you have an iced americano?",
        "option1": "아이스 아메리카노",
        "option2": "아메리카노",
        "option3": "아이스크림",
        "option4": "카라멜 마끼아또",
        "correctOption": 1,
        "category": "Level 1",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "[     ] 있어요?",
        "trans": "Is it fun?",
        "option1": "재미",
        "option2": "건강",
        "option3": "공부",
        "option4": "먹다",
        "correctOption": 1,
        "category": "Level 1",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "한국에 [     ] 있어요.",
        "trans": "There are pretty cafes in Korea.",
        "option1": "조용한 카페",
        "option2": "예쁜 카페",
        "option3": "맛있는 카페",
        "option4": "재미있는 카페",
        "correctOption": 2,
        "category": "Level 1",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "아니요, [     ] 없어요.",
        "trans": "No, I don't have money.",
        "option1": "간",
        "option2": "물",
        "option3": "돈",
        "option4": "돈을",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 1",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "네, [     ] 있어요.",
        "trans": "Yes, I have money.",
        "option1": "돈은",
        "option2": "돈을",
        "option3": "돌",
        "option4": "돈",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 1",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "이 드라마 [     ] 있어요?",
        "trans": "Is this drama fun?",
        "option1": "재미있는",
        "option2": "재미있다",
        "option3": "재미있을",
        "option4": "재미",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 1",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "[      ] 있어요?",
        "trans" : "Is there pineapple pizza?",
        "option1": "치즈 피자",
        "option2": "파인애플 피자",
        "option3": "아이스 아메리카노",
        "option4": "맛있는 피자",
        "correctOption": 2,
        "category": "Level 1",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "미국에 [      ] 없어요?",
        "trans": "Isn't there Kimchi in the US?",
        "option1": "참치",
        "option2": "김밥",
        "option3": "김치",
        "option4": "김치를",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 1",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "우리 수업 [      ] 있어요?",
        "trans": "Is our class fun?",
        "option1": "재미를",
        "option2": "재미는",
        "option3": "재미을",
        "option4": "재미",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 1",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
  

    
    {
        "question": "오늘 헬스장에서 [       ].",
        "trans": "Did you exercise at the gym today?",
        "option1": "여행했어요",
        "option2": "운전했어요",
        "option3": "연습했어요",
        "option4": "운동했어요",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 2",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
   
    {
        "question": "누구랑 [        ]?",
        "trans": "Who did you travel with?",
        "option1": "여행해요",
        "option2": "여행하다",
        "option3": "여행했어요",
        "option4": "여행가요",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 2",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "아니, 오늘 숙제 [      ].",
        "trans": "No, I didn't do my homework today.",
        "option1": "했어",
        "option2": "했어요",
        "option3": "안 했어요",
        "option4": "안 했어",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 2",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "어제 [     ] 했어요.",
        "trans": "I studied Korean yesterday.",
        "option1": "한국 공부",
        "option2": "공부 한국",
        "option3": "한국어 공부",
        "option4": "공부 한국어",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 2",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "어제 노래방에서 [      ].",
        "trans": "I sang at the karaoke yesterday.",
        "option1": "청소했어요",
        "option2": "노래했어요",
        "option3": "연습했어요",
        "option4": "전화했어요",
        "correctOption": 2,
        "category": "Level 2",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "정국아, 오늘 [       ]?",
        "trans": "Jungkook, did you do your homework today?",
        "option1": "했어",
        "option2": "안 했어",
        "option3": "숙제해",
        "option4": "숙제했어",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 2",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "오늘 블랙핑크 [      ].",
        "trans": "BlackPink came back today.",
        "option1": "컴백이예요",
        "option2": "컴백하다",
        "option3": "컴백해요",
        "option4": "컴백했어요",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 2",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },

    {
        "question": "오늘 3시간 동안 [       ].",
        "trans": "I drove for 3 hours today.",
        "option1": "비행했어요",
        "option2": "운전했어요",
        "option3": "운행했어요",
        "option4": "운동했어요",
        "correctOption": 2,
        "category": "Level 2",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "엄마, [      ] 다 했어요.",
        "trans": "Mom, I am done with cleaning.",
        "option1": "공부",
        "option2": "여행",
        "option3": "청소",
        "option4": "연습",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 2",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "제니는 미국에서 [       ].",
        "trans": "Jenny studied in the US.",
        "option1": "쇼핑 할 거예요",
        "option2": "쇼핑을 해요",
        "option3": "쇼핑을 좋아해요",
        "option4": "쇼핑했어요",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 2",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "저는 한국에 [        ]",
        "trans": "I want to go to Korea.",
        "option1": "가요",
        "option2": "가고 싶어요",
        "option3": "갈 거예요",
        "option4": "가고 싶어",
        "correctOption": 2,
        "category": "Level 3",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "오늘 뭐 [      ]?",
        "trans": "What do you want to eat today?",
        "option1": "먹어요",
        "option2": "먹었어요",
        "option3": "먹을 거예요",
        "option4": "먹고 싶어요",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 3",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "나도 같이 [       ].",
        "trans": "I want to go too.",
        "option1": "가고 싶어요",
        "option2": "가고 싶어",
        "option3": "가요",
        "option4": "가는 거예요",
        "correctOption": 2,
        "category": "Level 3",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "한국에서 제일 뭐 [       ]?",
        "trans": "What do you want to do the most in Korea?",
        "option1": "가고 싶어",
        "option2": "먹고 싶어",
        "option3": "해고 싶어",
        "option4": "하고 싶어",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 3",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "오늘 우리집에 [        ]?",
        "trans": "Do you want to come to my house today?",
        "option1": "가고 싶어요",
        "option2": "오고 싶어",
        "option3": "갈 거예요",
        "option4": "가고 싶어",
        "correctOption": 2,
        "category": "Level 3",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "뭐 [      ]?",
        "trans": "What do you want to drink?",
        "option1": "마셔요",
        "option2": "마시는 거예요",
        "option3": "마시고 싶어요",
        "option4": "마시고 싶은 거예요",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 3",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "무슨 책 [       ]?",
        "trans": "What book do you want to read?",
        "option1": "읽고 싶어요",
        "option2": "쓰고 싶어요",
        "option3": "배우고 싶어요",
        "option4": "읽으러 갈 거예요",
        "correctOption": 1,
        "category": "Level 3",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "토요일에 새로운 영화 [      ].",
        "trans": "I want to watch a new movie on Saturday.",
        "option1": "알고 싶어요",
        "option2": "가고 싶어요",
        "option3": "보고 싶어요",
        "option4": "오고 싶어요",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 3",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "제 지갑 [        ].",
        "trans": "I want to find my wallet.",
        "option1": "찾아요",
        "option2": "찾으러 갈 거예요",
        "option3": "찾았어요",
        "option4": "찾고 싶어요",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 3",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "생일선물로 아이폰을 [        ].",
        "trans": "I want to receive an iPhone as a birthday present.",
        "option1": "받을 거예요",
        "option2": "받아요",
        "option3": "받고 싶어요",
        "option4": "받았어요",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 3",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "저는 내년에 한국에 [      ].",
        "trans": "I will go to Korea next year.",
        "option1": "가요",
        "option2": "가고 싶어요",
        "option3": "갈 거예요",
        "option4": "가고 싶어",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 4",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "오늘 꼭 숙제를 [       ].",
        "trans": "I will do my homework today no matter what.",
        "option1": "해요",
        "option2": "할 거예요",
        "option3": "갈 거예요",
        "option4": "할지도 몰라요",
        "correctOption": 2,
        "category": "Level 4",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "오늘 꼭 숙제를 [       ].",
        "trans": "I will do my homework today no matter what.",
        "option1": "해요",
        "option2": "할 거예요",
        "option3": "갈 거예요",
        "option4": "할지도 몰라요",
        "correctOption": 2,
        "category": "Level 4",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "이번주에 한국어를 더 [       ].",
        "trans": "I will study more this week.",
        "option1": "공부 많이 할 거예요",
        "option2": "많이 할 공부예요",
        "option3": "공부 할 거예요 많이",
        "option4": "많이 공부 할 거예요",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 4",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "다음 주에 새로운 떡볶이 레시피를 [      ].",
        "trans": "I will try a new tteokbokki recipe next week.",
        "option1": "마주칠 거예요",
        "option2": "시작할 거예요",
        "option3": "시도할 거예요",
        "option4": "시도합니다",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 4",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "내일 아침에 [      ]?",
        "trans": "Will you exercise tomorrow morning?",
        "option1": "운동 하겠어요",
        "option2": "운동 하는 중이에요",
        "option3": "운동하려고 해요",
        "option4": "운동할 거예요",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 4",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "주말에 친구를 [        ].",
        "trans": "I will meet my friend on the weekend.",
        "option1": "놀 거예요",
        "option2": "만날 거예요",
        "option3": "만날까요",
        "option4": "만날게요",
        "correctOption": 2,
        "category": "Level 4",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "내일 도서관에 [      ]?",
        "trans": "Will you come to the library tomorrow?",
        "option1": "갈 거예요",
        "option2": "잘 거예요",
        "option3": "왔었을 거예요",
        "option4": "올 거예요",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 4",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "내일 아침에 일찍 [       ].",
        "trans": "I will wake up early tomorrow morning.",
        "option1": "잘 거예요",
        "option2": "할 거예요",
        "option3": "갈 거예요",
        "option4": "일어날 거예요",
        "correctOption": 4,
        "category": "Level 4",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "제 생일선물로 뭐 [          ]?",
        "trans": "What will you give me as a birthday present?",
        "option1": "걸 거예요",
        "option2": "할 거예요",
        "option3": "줄 거예요",
        "option4": "잘 거예요",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 4",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "trans": "What will you give me as a birthday present?",
        "option1": "걸 거예요",
        "option2": "할 거예요",
        "option3": "줄 거예요",
        "option4": "잘 거예요",
        "correctOption": 3,
        "category": "Level 5",
        "difficulty": "Beginner"
    }



]